Guide to the Records of the New York Foundling Hospital 1869-2009 MS 347
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV - Centers, Programs and Departments, Alphabetical, 1869-2008
  - Subseries IV.38 - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea, 1900-2000
    - St. Josephs-by-the-Sea - Miscellaneous narratives, reports, correspondence, brochure, clippings, circa 1909-2000 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 3)
    - St. Josephs-by-the-Sea - Photographic prints, postcards, 1937-1961 and undated (Offsite-box 41, Folder 4)
  - Subseries IV.39 - Seton Day Care, 1966-2001
    Materials include correspondence, proposals, annual reports, pamphlet, newsletters, and photographic prints.
    The Seton Day Care Center, founded in 1972, and Elizabeth Seton Pre-School, added in 1980, are Montessori-based child care and education programs financed by tuition, fees, and donations. Originally run out of the Foundling's main building, they moved to 1675 Third Avenue in 1988.
    - Seton Day Care - Correspondence, proposals, other documents, 1966 November 28 - 1989 July 27 and undated (Offsite-box 41, Folder 5)
    - Seton Day Care - 4 Annual Reports, 1978 January 15 - 1982 January 15 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 6)
    - Seton Day Care - Pamphlet, newsletter, reports, materials for parents, other materials, 1990 April - 2001 June and undated (Offsite-box 41, Folder 7)
    - Seton Day Care - Photographic prints, circa 1972-1998 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IV.40 - Sister Irene Residence
    The subseries contains one folder. The Sister Irene Residence was a 15-bed diagnostic residential program for girls, operating in 590 Avenue of the Americas from circa 1988 to 1994.
    - Sister Irene Residence - Correspondence re: closing, 1994 November 9 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 9)
  - Subseries IV.41 - Spiritual Development Department, circa 1980-2001
    The subseries contains two folders. The mission of the chaplains of the Spiritual Development Department is to nurture the spiritual lives of both Foundling clients and staff, through individual sessions, retreats, prayer services, support groups, bereavement counseling, funeral services, and other services.
    - Spiritual Development - draft policy regarding death, newsletters, brochure, other materials, circa 1982-2001 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 10)
    - Spiritual Development - Photographic prints, circa 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 11)
  - Subseries IV.42 - Staten Island Services, 1972 - circa 2005
    The Foundling's services on Staten Island include an emergency residential diagnostic center for children (The Staten Island Reception Center, opened in 1974), other group homes, foster boarding homes, and Staten Island Preventive Services, which provides counseling, skills training, recreation, substance abuse counseling, support groups, and other services for families and children.
    The subseries contains 12 folders of material documenting the development of these programs, in chronological order, with clippings and photographic prints arranged at the end.
    For similar programs, see subseries IV.4 - Agency-Operated Boarding Homes, IV.6 - Boarding Department and Foster Care, and IV.9 - Child Abuse Prevention Services. For another Staten Island program, see IV.38 - St. Joseph's-by-the-Sea.
    - Staten Island Services - correspondence, minutes, proposals, 1972 August 23 - 1974 December 5 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 12)
    - Staten Island Services - correspondence, memos, inspection, 1975 June 6 - 1982 October 28 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 13)
    - Staten Island Services - annual reports, procedure manual, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 14)
    - Staten Island Services - Mariners' Family Home - correspondence, appraisal, 1982 May 18 - 1984 December 5 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 15)
    - Staten Island Services - Proposal (physical and sexual abuse), 1982 October-November (Offsite-box 41, Folder 16)
    - Staten Island Services - correspondence, 1983 May 31 - 1984 February 21 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 17)
    - Staten Island Services - Proposal - foster care/child abuse prevention), 1983 September 9 - November 10 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 1)
    - Staten Island Services - pamphlet, booklets, fund-raising packet, memo, circa 1983-2005 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Staten Island Services - proposal - adolescent pregnancy prevention and services, 1984 November - 1985 January (Offsite-box 42, Folder 3)
    - Staten Island Services - proposal - general preventive services, circa 1999 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 4)
    - Staten Island Services - clippings, 1983 December - 1998 February (Offsite-box 42, Folder 5)
    - Staten Island Services - photographic prints, circa 1975 - 1995 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 6)
  - Subseries IV.43 - Temporary Care Intake, 1962-circa 1990s
    - Temporary Care Intake - clippings, one photographic print, 1962, 1976, circa 1990's (Offsite-box 42, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IV.44 - Training and Development Department, 1997 and undated
    - Training and Development Department - catalogue, pamphlet and memos 1977, and undated photographic print, 1997 and undated (Offsite-box 42, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IV.45 - Volunteers, 1946-2000
    The subseries contains reports, manuals, minutes, newsletters, programs, clippings, and photographic prints and negatives. For other volunteer materials, see Ladies Auxiliary and other Fundraising Associations (subseries IV.22).
    - Volunteers - reports ("summaries") of department, annual reports, 1946, 1955, 1957, 1961, 1977, 1981 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 9)
    - Volunteers - "The Volunteer" newsletter, vol.2, no.4 and vol.5, no.2, 1948 January, 1950 November (Offsite-box 42, Folder 10)
    - Volunteers - Manuals, 1952, 1975, 2000 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 11)
    - Volunteers - Minutes of volunteer supervisors' meetings 1955-1959, 1965-1966, and annual report 1954, 1955 January 11 - 1966 March 8 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 12)
    - Volunteers - programs and liturgies for awards services, 1962-1964, 1966, 1994, 1999 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 13)
    - Volunteers - photographic prints and negatives, circa 1946-1999 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 14)
    - Volunteers - Texaco Topics Vol.22, No.10 (article on volunteers, p. 4), 1953 December (Offsite-box 43, Folder 1)
    - Volunteers - Equinews Vol.1, No.10 (article on volunteer aides p. 14), 1957 September (Offsite-box 43, Folder 2)
    - Volunteers - Pfizer Scene, Vol.11, No.9 (article on volunteer aides p. 16), 1963 November (Offsite-box 43, Folder 3)
    - Volunteers - Photocopied clippings and disbound periodical articles, circa 1947-1970 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 4)
  - Subseries IV.46 - West End Intergenerational Residence, 1987-1997
    The West End Intergenerational Residence, on 83rd Street and West End Avenue in Manhattan, opened in 1989 as a mixed-age housing, education, and social service program, providing transitional housing for single mothers with pre-school aged children, as well as permanent housing for low-income senior citizens.
    The subseries contains 9 folders. See also IV.19-Housing.
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - proposal (parts 1 and 2 of 3), 1987 June 15 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 5)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - proposal (part 3 of 3), 1987 June 15 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 6)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - Part 900 Regulations, circa 1989 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 7)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - Rights, Responsibilities and Rules manual (draft), circa 1990-1997 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 8)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - Newsletters (6), 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 9)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - pamphlets and invitation, 1994 and undated (Offsite-box 43, Folder 10)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - financial statements, 1994 October 31 - 1996 July 9 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 11)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - meeting materials, 1997 March 13 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 12)
    - West End Intergenerational Residence - clippings, circa 1990-1995 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 13)
  - Subseries IV.47 - Westchester Office, circa 1965
    The Westchester Office opened in 1965 as a branch of the Boarding Department. The subseries contains one folder with photographic prints and one clipping.
    - Westchester Office - photographic prints, clipping, circa 1965 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 14)
- Series V - Records of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1875-2001
  The series contains minutes, correspondence, reports, legal documents, pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, photographic prints and other records of the St. Agatha Home for Children 1875-1977, and the St. Agatha Home of the New York Foundling Hospital 1977-2001, in 7 boxes and 15 volumes. One additional item is also housed in a separate oversized (OS) box, noted in the container list.
  The series is arranged in 5 subseries:
  V.1 - St. Agatha Incorporation and By-Laws, 1884-1973
  V.2 - St. Agatha Minutes and Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1887-1977
  V.3 - St. Agatha Reports and Inspections, 1885-1955
  V.4 - St. Agatha Records, Chronological, 1875-2001
  V.5 - St. Agatha Clippings and Photographic Materials, ca. 1949-1999
  Additional documentation of the St. Agatha Home can be found in Series II, Annual Reports of the Foundling (1977, 1981 and 1984 specifically focus on St. Agatha); and Series I and III, Minutes and Administrative Records of the Foundling.
  The St. Agatha Home for Children in Nanuet, New York, was founded in 1884 by the Sisters of Charity, on 16 acres of land donated in 1875 by John Reid. Its mission was to be a home and trade school for orphans and neglected children. Most children were referred by the New York City courts. Over the years, land adjacent to the original property was purchased, and various buildings and wings were erected, including a building which functioned first as a "Preventorium" for sick children from 1913-1945, and later as a school. In the 1950's and 1960's, the St. Agatha Home consisted of about two dozen buildings on about 172 acres of land. In 1950, approximately 600 children lived there, and 358 in 1967.
  Beginning in 1969, St. Agatha decentralized, operating small group homes in Rockland County, the Bronx and Staten Island, providing community-based care for youth awaiting possible foster placement. In addition, it ran prevention programs, and opened two non-secure-detention shelters for juveniles in the criminal justice system. In the 1970's St. Agatha's struggled financially, relying on city funds during the years of the city's fiscal crisis, while the percentage of teenagers and children with severe problems and special needs increased. The St. Agatha Home merged into the NY Foundling Hospital in 1977. Consolidation of two Sisters of Charity institutions providing related services would enable more effective coordinated care.
  After the merger, the St. Agatha Home of the New York Foundling established several new critical care programs for developmentally disabled children and adults, programs for Vietnamese boat children, and shelters for homeless youth, among other services.
  The latest material in this series dates from 2001. In 2005, the St. Agatha Home closed and the property in Nanuet was sold.
  - Subseries V.1 - St. Agatha Incorporation and By-Laws, 1884-1973
    - St. Agatha - Certificate of Incorporation (typescript copy), 1884 November 29 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - By-Laws, 1931, 1934, 1942, 1950 and undated (Offsite-box 44, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - Certificate of Change of Purposes and related correspondence, 1965 October (Offsite-box 44, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha - By-Laws and related correspondence, 1972 September - 1973 September (Offsite-box 44, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha - By-Laws, 1973 November 28 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V.2 - St. Agatha Minutes and Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1887-1977
    The subseries consists of Minutes 1877-1977, bound in volumes, followed by reports to the Board of Trustees in folders 1936-1961. A small quantity of additional board meeting documents, particularly from the time of the merger with the Foundling and shortly thereafter, may be found in subseries V.5, St. Agatha Administrative Records Chronological.
    Minutes of the Foundling are in Series I.
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1887 May 24 - 1909 January 11 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 47)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1909 April 16 - 1925 November 9 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 48)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1926 February 8 - 1933 May 9 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 49)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1933 November 13 - 1942 March 10 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 50)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1942 June 10 - 1951 June 30 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 51)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1951 September 12 - 1961 September 12 (Offsite-box 82, Volume 52)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1961 November 10 - 1963 March 4 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 53)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1963 June 6 - 1966 March 8 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 54)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1966 June 2 - 1968 December 5 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 55)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1969 January 17 - 1971 June 2 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 56)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1971 September 16 - 1973 November 19 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 57)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1974 March 18 - 1975 December 11 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 58)
    - Minutes of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1976 March 4 - 1977 June 14 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 59)
    - St. Agatha - Quarterly Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1936-1943 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - Quarterly Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1944-1951 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Quarterly Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - Quarterly Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - Quarterly Reports to the Board of Trustees, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 10)
  - Subseries V.3 - St. Agatha Reports and Inspections, 1885-1995
    - St. Agatha - Reports sent to Albany, 1885-1900 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 60)
    - St. Agatha - Managers Record (visits/inspections by town Board of Health among others), 1912-1943 (Offsite-box 83, Volume 61)
    - St. Agatha - Financial Reports to NYC Comptroller (missing 1935), 1933-1939 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - Reports and Inspections - State Department of Social Welfare, 1933-1944 and 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - Report of Inspection by Catholic Charities (2 copies), 1938 May (Offsite-box 45, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha - Financial Reports to Catholic Charities, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha - Miscellaneous Inspections (Dept. of Public Charities, Insurance, unidentified), 1905-1933 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V.4 - St. Agatha Records, Chronological, 1875-2001
    The subseries contains records of the St. Agatha Home, including but not limited to administrative correspondence, pamphlets, reports, newsletters and legal documents including petitions and agreements for the merger with the Foundling and deeds.
    The subseries is arranged with one folder of histories of the St. Agatha Home at the front, followed by folders of documents arranged chronologically by the earliest date on the folder.
    - St. Agatha - Histories of the St. Agatha Home, circa 1898-2000 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - Property - Deeds and Easements, 1875-1979 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1876 January - 1949 June 9 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - Contract with N.Y.C. for care of city charges (526 children) - original and copy, 1912 January 23 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - Bethlehem Preventorium appeals, circa 1913 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative correspondence - copies glued in volume, 1916 February - 1922 May 3 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - Activities for children (clubs, summer program, classes, commencement, confirmation) - programs, memos, other materials, 1917 May - 1951 May and undated (Offsite-box 46, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative correspondence - copies glued in volume, 1918 November 9 - December 7 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha - Correspondence with Roman Catholic Orphan Asylum (includes RCOA minutes), 1918, 1929, 1938, 1960, 1962 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha - Summary of services, 1950 January (Offsite-box 46, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - "The Hill" - student publication by St. Agatha teenage girls, circa 1950-1965 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative correspondence - miscellaneous, 1951 March 28 - 1959 January 17 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Dedication ceremonies - invitations, speeches, 1952-1964 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - 4-page typescript appeal (2 copies), circa 1953 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - Pamphlets, circa 1953, 1968 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha Alumni Association - Minutes and correspondence, 1956 July 4 - 1957 December 18 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 11)
    - St. Agatha - 75th anniversary newsletter and commemorative medallion, 1959 May 13 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 12)
    - St. Agatha - Correspondence, reports, announcement of first group home, 1960-1973 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 13)
    - St. Agatha - Memos re: property, 1967 December 8 - 2000 October 17 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 14)
    - St. Agatha - Financial statements, 1968 June 30 - 1969 May 29 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 15)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Merger evaluation report, 1969 May (Offsite-box 46, Folder 16)
    - St. Agatha - "Plot Plan" of property (oversize), 1973 October 16 (Offsite-box OS 1, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - Newsletters - Vol.1, No.1 and Vol.1, No.2 and unidentified other (pages missing), 1975 and circa 1974 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 17)
    - St. Agatha - Pamphlets, brochures, circa 1975-2005 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative correspondence, reports, memos, 1976 January 5 - 1976 March 23 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - Financial reports, 1976 March 31 - 1977 June 7 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha - Correspondence, reports, memos, board materials, 1976 April 19 - 1976 September 20 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha - Operating budget for fiscal year ending June 30, 1977, circa 1976 September (Offsite-box 47, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - Administrative correspondence, reports, memos, board materials, 1976 October 5 - 1977 January 6 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - Departmental reports and related correspondence, 1976 November 9 - 1977 May 31 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Resolution of the Foundling and St. Agatha approving merger, 1976 December 16 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Merger report for N.Y. State Board of Social Welfare, plan of merger, and related correspondence from Cardinal Cooke, et. al., 1977 January 28 - May 24 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Merger application - legal document, 1977 February 14 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Merger application - legal documents, 1977 March 2 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 11)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Certificate of Merger and related documents, 1977 March 2 - 1978 July 10 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 12)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Board materials, reports, correspondence, 1977 February 24 - June 14 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 13)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Board materials, reports, correspondence, 1979 June 5 - November 29 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Expansion of Health-Related Facility - application and correspondence, 1980 October 8 - 1981 May 20 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Property Analysis report, 1981 May (Offsite-box 48, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling - Reports, correspondence, board materials, circa 1982 - 1983 August (Offsite-box 48, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha Services - memos, reports, circa 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - Social Workers' Manual, 1983 July - 1984 November 20 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - "Project Turning Point" Runaway Youth Program - proposals, reports, correspondence, clippings, pamphlet, invitation, other materials, 1984 August 17 - 2000 August 30 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - programs and other materials for centennial celebrations, 1984 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - O.M.R.D.D./Respite Program - newsletter, clippings, program, certificate, other materials, folder 1 of 3, 1984-1999 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - O.M.R.D.D./Respite Program - report, pamphlet, other materials - folder 2 of 3, 1988-2001 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha - O.M.R.D.D./Respite Program - Resource Manual - folder 3 of 3, 1998 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 11)
    - St. Agatha - Westchester Independent Living Ladder Program - contract and budget, 1985 January 17 - November 4 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - Unaccompanied Refugee Minors Program - invitation, newsletter, proposal, 1986 April 3 - 1992 November 18 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - report on proposed new school, circa 1987 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha - day care proposal, 1987 November 6 - 1988 March 11 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 4)
    - St. Agatha - Information about programs 1966-2001 (assembled 1987-2001) - Includes Polaroid photographs, circa 1987 - 2001 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - Ulster County Prevention Services - proposals, memos, invitations, other materials, 1990 - 2001 March 7 and undated (Offsite-box 49, Folder 6)
    - St. Agatha - Refugee Assistance Program - correspondence, memos, 1992 May 11 - 1995 January 17, and 1999 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Information on programs and services, circa 1993 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - Senator Holland Reforming Welfare Hearings - correspondence, memos, other materials, 1993 November 19 - 1996 February 26 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - Client testimonial correspondence and other documents, invitations, programs, 1994-2000 and 1969 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha/Foundling Property - appraisal, plans, correspondence, legal documents, 1997 October 30 - 1999 February 24 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 11)
    - St. Agatha Roll Book (statistics at facilities by month), 1998 January - December (Offsite-box 49, Folder 12)
    - St. Agatha - Child Care Supervisor Manual, circa 1999 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 13)
    - "St. Agatha News" - newsletters (9 issues), 1999 October 1 - 2000 December 21 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 1)
    - St. Agatha - newsletter (for group homes), circa 2000 October (Offsite-box 50, Folder 2)
    - St. Agatha - N.Y.S. Office of Children and Family Services Data Warehouse draft, circa 2000 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 3)
    - St. Agatha Equestrian Program (Children of Promise Stables) - proposal and dedication materials, circa 2000 - 2001 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 4)
  - Subseries V.5 - St. Agatha Clippings and Photographic Materials, circa 1949-1999
    The 9 folders in the subseries are arranged as follows: clippings chronological; followed by mixed clippings and photographic prints; followed by photographic prints (exteriors); followed by photographic prints chronological. A few additional photographic prints may be found among the material in Box 49, Folder 5.
    - St. Agatha - Clippings, 1949-1969 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 5)
    - St. Agatha - Clippings, 1979-1999 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 6)